https://edlpackaging.com/privacy-policy/

What information do we collect?
We collect the information you provide when filling out a form.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
To improve our website
To improve our service
To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your request
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
Your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the content or service requested.
This does not include trusted third parties who might assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or serving you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Non personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.
Third-party links
Occasionally we may provide links to resources provided by third party organizations that have separate and independent privacy policies. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. However, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and provide only links to sites we believe to be trustworthy.
Online privacy policy only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not information collected offline.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this site. The policy was last modified October 27, 2016.
Contacting us
If you have questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at:
EDL Packaging Engineers, Inc.
1260 Parkview Road
Green Bay, WI 54304
T: (920) 336-7744
